

Thisura Rasanjana

UI/UX Enginee

NATIONALITY - Sri Lankan DATE OF BIRTH - 21st May, 1997

CONTACT

+94 76 6 488 168

krtrasanjana@gmail.com

http://www.thisura.xyz/

EDUCATION

BSc(Hons) Computer Science

0

- 2nd Class Upper Division

- NSBM Green University (Offered by UCD Ireland)

- GPA - 3.45

△ Certificate Course in English Language

- NIBM Colombo 07

Passed GCE A/L in Physical science stream

- Mahanama College Colombo 03

PROFILE

I completed my higher education in April 2021 and started my career as a Full Stack Software Developer. My total work experience period was 2 and half year but I found my true ability and desire in this career path about a year ago. Asp .Net, Microsoft SQL, SSRS, C# are the most familiar technologies I have worked in my 1 and half years of career journey. But about a year ago I realized my own technical and designing skills(user empathy), I started to work as an UI / UX engineer. Since I am new to this field I always try to sharpen my skills for this position. And I always try to give my maximum creative potential to the company I work for. I have a strong belief in my abilities and my only goal is to further improve them and move to the top of this field. As an UI / UX Engineer, I accept any challenge that comes my way and face it successfully.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML/CSS/BOOTSTRAP/JS

ANGULAR/ NODE JS/ TYPESCRIPT

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP/ ADOBE XD/ ZEPLIN

ASP.NET WEB FORMS/ C#

MICROSOFT SQL/ SSRS

Also I have experience with React JS, React Native, C, Java, Little bit in Ionic Framework and GitHub, GitLab, Microsoft Azure, Bitbucket and Jira as cloud platforms.

WORK EXPERIENCES

- Full Stack Software Developer
 [At Softlogic Life IT, Nugegoda] Sep. 2019 to Present
- Intern Mobile Application Developer
 [At Ceylon Petroleum Storage Terminals LTD,
 Kolonnawa] Sep. 2018 to Dec. 2018
- Founder Designer
 ['The Social Media Guy' Startup company]
 Aug. 2019 to Present

CTO - Web & Front-end Developer
 ['Team NextScope' Startup Web & Software

development company | Dec. 2018 to Feb. 2020

CHARACTER REFERENCES

MR. JANITH SHIRANTHA General Manager, Softlogic Life IT, Nugegoda +94 7 77 596 263 MR. VARUNA GUNASEKARA Assistant Manager Information Systems CPSTL, Kolonnawa +94 7 77 596 263